<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cocobelly Bites</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cocobelly Bites</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-us/</guid>
      <description>About Us As sisters, we&amp;rsquo;ve had the honor of being surrounded by amazing home cooks, so great tasting food has always been a staple for us. Food is very often tied to folk&amp;rsquo;s best memories with family and friends. So we want to share our knowledge of the Jamaican cuisine as a way to preserve our childhood memories, and to create new memories for others.
Paula Cooking and just living life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/</guid>
      <description>2023 Calendar of Events Month of July 2023 Come visit us in Somerville
Date Description Mon 7/3 Nibble Kitchen Popup within Bow Market Sat 7/8 Somerville Farmer’s Market in Union Square Sat 7/22 Somerville Farmer’s Market in Union Square Monday 7/3: Popup in Nibble Kitchen Have you been wanting to eat a hot patty on the spot? Well this popup is just what you need, so come visit us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/homepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/homepage/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/photo-album/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photo-album/</guid>
      <description>Photo Album June 19th: Nibble Kitchen Popup on Juneteenth Many THANKS to everyone that dropped into the popup at Nibble Kitchen in Bow Market to enjoy a hot patty, side of plaintains and sorrel refresher. Going in we were unsure of how many diners would come out on a Monday afternoon. However we were pleasantly suprised and promise to have more at our next popup.
May 27th: Somerville Farmer&amp;rsquo;s Market Introducing the market shoppers to our handmade Jamaican bites on a nice sunny Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
